So you are a women in the mid-18th century
所以你是18世纪中叶的女性
You are getting dressed and in order to do that
你在穿衣服，为了做到这一点
you put on your shift, your petticoat, your hoops
你穿上你的衬衣，衬裙，发箍
because you feel like being, a bit posh
因为你觉得自己挺时髦
Your second petticoat, your stays, your pocket
您的第二件衬裙，您的胸衣，口袋
your gown, your cap, fichu, ruffles, etc.
您的礼服，帽子，绒毛，荷叶边等
Or perhaps you are a woman in the mid-19th century
也许您是19世纪中叶的女性
in which case you’ve got your chemise
在这种情况下，你有自己的连衣裙
your corset, crinoline, petticoat, skirt, bodice, shoes, shawls, and bonnet
您的紧身胸衣，短裙，衬裙，裙子，鞋子，披肩和帽子
Or maybe you’re an Elizabethan where instead you are opting for
或者，也许您是伊丽莎白时期的人，而您却选择了
伊丽莎白时期：英国伊丽莎白一世女王统治英国的一个纪元（1558年－1603年）。
smock, partlet, pair of bodies, roll, farthingale
罩衫，无袖衣，紧身衣，裙卷，裙撑
underskirt, overskirt, bodice, cap, and ruff
短裙，超短裙，紧身胸衣，帽子和围脖
The question looms eternally with all those layers interconnecting and overlapping
一层层的服饰交织覆盖，导致了一个永恒的问题
especially around the waist area
特别是在腰部周围
How did anyone get anything off efficiently to pee multiple times per day?
每天该怎么方便高效地脱衣服上厕所？
You’ll perhaps notice the one garment not included in your daily dressing
您可能会注意到日常穿着中未包括的一件衣服
throughout any of these periods is
它并未出现在之前的列举中
in fact, we today would think of as “underwear”
实际上，我们如今称之为“内衣”
for this simple logical reason that
由于这个简单的逻辑原因
for the most part women just didn’t wear them
在大多数情况下，女性只是不穿它们
But for the sake of this video by the way
但是为了这个视频
I’m going to referring to this particular garment as “underwear"
我将把这件特定的服装称为“内衣”
and not meaning the general concepts of garments
并不意味着我们平常所指的那种
that women wear underneath the closing since
那些女性穿在其他衣服之内的衣服
yes they did indeed wear many more things
是的，她们如今确实在其他衣服下
under their other things than we do today
多穿了很多东西
But the word “pants” confuses the Americans
但是“裤子”一词使美国人感到困惑
and “panties” confuses the British
和“内裤”使英国人困惑
and any more obscure reference to said small clothes
还有对这些小衣服的晦涩参考
is just generally unnecessarily unfair to our multilingual friends
对我们多语种的朋友来说通常只是不必要地不公平
So underwear, it shall be
所以，内衣应该是
I say women “for the most part” didn’t I wear underwear
我说女人“大部分”不穿内衣
because as is the precarious way of history
因为这是不稳定的历史方式
we are all just interpreting the selected evidence
我们都在解释特定的证据
that happens to survive to us
碰巧能支持我们的观点
However, many centuries later and that subsequently there is no such thing
但是，许多世纪以后，后来没有这种东西
as a straightforward fact when speaking about things that
当谈到那些
we have no firsthand experience in
我们没有以下方面的第一手资料
And, well, this no underwear thing is where the evidence points us at present
而且，不穿内衣的事，这是目前证据所体现的
there will undoubtably be uncovered at some point in the future
毫无疑问，将来某个时候会发现
Some evidence to suggest that one woman somewhere was
一些证据表明某些地方的女性
in fact, regularly wearing what we might call underwear today
实际上，经常穿我们如今称之为内衣的衣服
There is for example the textile finds uncovered in Lengberg Castle in Austria
例如，在奥地利的Lengberg城堡中发现了纺织品
including this pair of what distinctly looks to be underwear
包括这对看起来很像内衣的东西
and although confirmably similar in style to the undergarments worn by men
并且尽管在样式上肯定与男人穿着的内衣相似
in the circa-15th century period attributed as the date of origin
它起源于约15世纪时期
it was found amongst fragments of a distinctly women’s undergarment
是在明显的女性内衣的碎片中发现的
So, anything is possible
所以，一切皆有可能
But for the most part, evidence or the comparative lack of surviving evidence thereof
但是在大多数情况下，还是比较缺乏现存的证据
and not just surviving garments but lack of written indications
不单是遗留下来的服饰，而且缺乏书面资料
in journals, inventories, dictionaries, and wills
在报纸，清单，字典和遗嘱中
indicates that for the most part, these garments were not a prevalent part of
这表明通常来说，直到19世纪前
the average woman’s wardrobe until about the 19th century
这些服饰依然不太流行
But we’ll get to that
但是我们依然可以研究它
When you think about it, it kind of make sense
试想一下
when you already got layers of shifts and petticoats and skirt’s going on
当你已经有很多衣服，衬裙和裙子的时候
with the lower half of your outfit
在你的下半身
who would have said,
谁会说，
“Hey, you know what would be a really great idea?”
“嘿，你知道什么是一个好主意吗？”
And additional little garment that we have to surgically extract from under our skirts
还有我们必须通过像外科手术一样从裙子下提取的其他小衣服
and stays every time we have to pee
并在每次必须尿尿时停留
It is far easier not to have extract anything at all
根本不提取任何东西要容易得多
but rather to just lift up your skirts
而是举起你的裙子
position your chamber pot accordingly and go
相应地放置便壶并开始
“But wait!” I hear you ask,
“可是等等！”我听你问
“What was one supposed to do at that time of moon
“在来月经的时候应该做什么？
when one might actually prefer to have something a bit tighter going on,
当一个人实际上可能想穿更紧身一些的，
despite the additional inconvenience?”
尽管还有其他不便？”
References to 18th century menstrual management are rare
很少有资料提及18世纪的月经管理
save for the implication of an apron being used
除了使用围裙的含义
Abby Cox has experimented with a theory of
艾比·考克斯在她的频道上尝试了以下理论
using an apron made of absorbent diaper woven cloth on her channel
使用由吸收性尿布编织布制成的围裙
if you care to investigate in greater detail on this subject
如果您想对此问题进行更详细的研究
There are copious references and advertisements
有大量的参考文献和广告显示
by the latter part of the 19th century for reusable
到19世纪后期出现的重复利用和
and later disposable towels that could be clipped to sanitary belts
之后出现的可以夹在卫生带上的一次性毛巾
and sanitary belts as well as absorbent aprons worn to
和卫生带以及穿在身上的吸收性围裙
protect the back of the skirts
来保护裙子的后部
were prevalent in advertisements by the early 20th century
在20世纪初期流行于广告中
The transition from no drawers to yes drawers is not one happens overnight
从无裤子到有裤子的转变不是一朝一夕的事
but is one that occurs gradually sometime around the 19th century
但是是在19世纪某个时候逐渐发生的一种
such that the Workwomen’s Guide states by 1838
例如《女企业家指南》在1838年之前
that drawers are, quote,
裤子据说是
“worn by men, women, and children of all classes and almost all ages”
“所有年龄段，几乎所有年龄段的男人，女人和孩子都穿着”
I should note that Queen Victoria ascended the English throne
我应该指出，维多利亚女王登上了英国王位
only one year before in 1837
仅在1837年之前的一年
and drawers have already apparently become a ubiquitous necessity
裤子显然已经成为普遍的必需品
according to the reference from 1838
根据1838年的参考资料
So we can’t necessarily blame delicate Victorian sensibilities for their adoption
因此，我们不一定会因采用维多利亚时代的精致感而受到指责
Visual representations of fashionable dress continue
时装的视觉表现继续
to depict commando ladies all the way up until at least 1811
描绘突击队女士直到1811年
But this image, dated a mere seven years later to 1818
但是这张影像，距今仅七年，直到1818年
is already showing a woman wearing drawers
已经显示出一个穿着裤子的女人
as part of her usual dressing routine
作为她惯常的穿衣习惯的一部分
Much like a change from the term stays to corset
很像保留词的变化
The adoption of drawers wasn’t a transition that happened over night
裤子的采用并不是一夜发生的
but rather more likely over the course of a generation
但在一代人的过程中更有可能
Nevertheless, despite the adoption of drawers under dresses in the 19th century
然而，尽管在19世纪采用了裤子在衣服下面
these still didn’t pose any impediment to peeing
这些仍然对小便没有任何阻碍
as the vast majority of surviving examples
作为大多数尚存的例子
the crotch seam of 19th century drawers
19世纪裤子的开缝
and later combinations was generally left open
后来的组合通常都处于开放状态
I say generally because there are examples of sewn drawers that
我之所以这么说是因为有一些缝制裤子的例子
if museum dating can be trusted would have existed towards
如果博物馆标注的时间可靠的话
the mid to early part of the 19th century
十九世纪中叶
well before sewn drawers became widespread
缝制裤子流行之前
But the circumstances in which these were worn
但是这些衣服的穿着情况
whether by a staunchly anti-corset lady
是否由坚定的紧身胸衣女士
an invalid or just someone particularly committed
残疾人或只是特别犯案的人
to completely undressing in order to pee is unknown
完全脱了衣服来小便是未知的
And of course, it is also unconfirmable as to
当然，对于
whether or not these garments even were worn
这些衣服是否穿过
considering that the ones that survive seem to be—surprisingly pristine
考虑到那些幸存者似乎是原始的
It is around the very end of 19th century and into the Edwardian era
大约在19世纪末，进入爱德华时代
爱德华时期：英国国王爱德华七世在位时期的一段时期（1901年－1910年）。
that we begin to see this seam being closed
我们开始看到这个接缝已经闭合
first with buttons in some surviving examples
首先在一些尚存的示例中使用按钮
so that the seam could still be opened easily
这样就可以轻松打开接缝
without the entire garment needing to be extracted from under the corset
无需从紧身胸衣下面抽出整件衣服
and finally sewn up completely as we approach the 1920s
最终在我们接近19世纪20年代时被完全缝制
The simplification and shortening of skirts
裙子的简化和缩短
and the adoption of the brassiere in place of the corset
并采用胸罩代替紧身胸衣
are likely significant factors in this evolution
可能是这一演变过程中的重要因素
since fewer foundation layers simultaneously
因为减少了打底的层次
meant less layers of protection and concealment
同时意味着更少的保护和隐蔽
but also, easier potential for extraction of a pair of closed-seam underwear
而且，更容易提取一条封闭缝内衣
at necessary moments
在必要的时候
The term of “pair of underwear”, by the way
顺便说一下，“内衣”一词
comes from their ancestral pair of drawers
来自他们祖先的裤子
and the two individual legs from which they were comprised
和组成它们的两条腿
The prevalent adoption of underwear is thus a surprisingly recent event
因此，普遍采用内衣是一个令人惊讶的近期事件
There is evidence of men’s underpants occurring throughout periods of history
有证据表明，男性内裤在整个历史时期都在发生
from the linen briefs of the medieval periods
从中世纪的亚麻内裤
to the occasional evidence of linen drawers in the 18th century
到18世纪偶尔出现的亚麻制裤子证据
despite most visual evidence suggesting that drawers were likewise uncommon
尽管大多数视觉证据表明裤子同样罕见
in menswear by this time as well
这次也穿男装
But this isn’t wholly irrelevant to the dilemma of peeing
但这与小便的困境并不完全无关
since men’s style of dress were
因为男人的着装风格是
if not less layered
如果不少分层
at least constructed so that they were easily dismantlable
至少构造易于拆解
for peeing purposes with codpieces, fall fronts and button flies
搭配，前缀和纽扣蝇
So that was me sufficiently taking six whole minutes longer than it should have
所以我足够花整整六分钟的时间
to answer this exceedingly simple question
回答这个极其简单的问题
but if you are not here for unnecessarily passionate explorations
但是如果您不在这里进行不必要的热情求知
into the urinary habits of pre-20th century humans then honestly
坦白讲讲20世纪前人类的小便习惯
I don’t even know why you’re still here
我甚至不知道你为什么还在这里